The concert that was supposed
to happen on the Zwei Islands
has been officially moved to next month.
As such, we'd like to ask Little Garden,
who will handle security for the event,
for a little favor of sorts.
There's someone Sakura
would like as her bodyguard.
Bodyguard
Hayato!
Now, Hayato!
Right!
Wait!
Damn it. I'm out of energy...
Just kidding.
He's got a muzzle there?!
Focus...
Don't let it take over.
I can do this!
Fritz!
You've got me.
I surrender.
That was amazing! They're all too good!
Kisaragi-kun in particular was so fast at the end,
I couldn't even see him!
Yeah!
People in Selections are
really on a different level.
Yeah!
Good work, Hayato.
You're able to control
your Variant pretty well now.
Yeah, I hope so.
I didn't think you'd cut through my attack.
I thought we'd gotten stronger
in the month since we came to this school,
but I guess getting into Selections
is still a pipe dream.
That's not true.
Not many people could force Hayato
into his full-body armament.
Yeah, I guess!
Just goes to show that
we're getting stronger too.
Yeah!
Wait! Stop patting me on the head.
Kisaragi Hayato,
Claire-sama calls for you.
You have a Selections mission.
A bodyguard for Kirishima Sakura?
She supposedly requested you herself.
She'd like you to be there for the concert
on the Zwei Islands next weekend.
Why me?
I didn't get an exact answer for that.
But so long as the Savage may still be
lurking on the Zwei Island chain,
all the VIPs there need protection.
And in fact, we detected seven Savages
during our action last month.
But we only fought three of them.
That's correct.
The other four were said to have been
shot down before they made landfall.
However, we found the remains
of only one of them.
So they might be up and about somewhere?
Another three of those monsters?
It could be a dangerous mission.
Kisaragi Hayato, what do you intend to do?
I accept.
Please let me do this.
Good answer.
You'll be giving up your weekend,
so you should receive some moderate pay.
Is there anything else
you'd like to ask for?
Oh, in that case,
there is one thing...
Oh, Nii-san!
What?!
You're going to be Sakura-san's bodyguard?!
K-Karen, you're being too loud.
I... I'm sorry.
Hold on a second.
I need to take a deep breath.
This all seems like a dream.
You get to see Sakura-san...
I'd love to see her too, just once.
You'll get your wish.
Huh?
I had them get you a ticket for the concert.
What? Really?!
Yeah.
I asked the president,
and she got one especially for you.
The girl with the golden drills?
The president's pretty nice, after all.
Oh, right!
Actually, there's something
I've been worried about.
Worried about?
I checked your fortune just now,
and it seems you need to watch out
for women and water.
Women and water?
Yeah. So make sure you're really careful
with water, and especially women.
Sure. Got it.
Hm? Is there something else?
If you could...
...try to get me Sakura-san's autograph!
Hayato. Hayato.
Good morning.
We've made it to the Zwei Islands.
Emile! You're here again?!
We don't make shore very often.
I wanted to go on a date with you.
You don't have anything to do
in the morning, right?
Sorry, I got word yesterday that the mission
will begin in the morning instead.
What?!
Sorry.
I see.
Oh, well. Work is work.
That really sucks, though.
Good luck today.
Kisaragi Hayato, are you ready?
Yes. I've got my tracer and N-tranquilizers
right here.
This'll be your first bodyguard
mission. Keep alert.
Right.
I'm so happy I could come back.
Nice to meet you.
I'm the XO on the Little Garden,
Liddy Steinberg.
I'm Kirishima Sakura.
Nice to meet you.
So you're Kisaragi Hayato-san, right?
Is it always like this?
No, this is actually light.
Seriously?
Why did someone so famous
want me as a bodyguard?
What's the matter?
Nothing at all.
Do you have a favorite song of mine?
Uh... well...
I'm sorry. I don't listen to much music.
I see.
But my sister's a fan. An ardententent...
Huh?
You really don't have it together, do you?
It's okay. I don't mind.
Oh, and you don't have to try to be so polite.
Forget the formalities,
and just call me "Sakura."
Here you go.
You're not going in?
I believe there's something
you need to do first, as my bodyguard.
Ah, yeah. I should check the room.
Let's see... The tracer...
Here it is.
Are you really the Kisaragi Hayato?
W-Well, that is my name...
But uh... I've never been a bodyguard before.
Sorry, I'll do my check. Hold on a second.
All clear. You can come in.
Looks like we finally get some time alone.
Hey, Hayato.
Wanna get married?
This is you, right?
Why do you...
I found it on the Cybernet.
Though it's been erased now.
I saw this and took an interest in you...
The hero who saved the Zwei Islands.
You're a little different than I expected.
You're pretty awkward.
But I think that's pretty cute.
What?
Hey, want to go out?
With an eye on getting married, of course.
Wh-Why?
Hm? You're not happy I'm hitting on you?
Do you have someone already?
Do you?
H-Hold on a second.
Why are you talking about going out?
The miracle couple: the Diva of the World
and the Genius Slayer.
Wouldn't that be great?
I think the media would eat it up, too.
Huh? The media...?
We'd hold a press conference, right?
We'd use the Zwei Islands,
the place we met, for the location.
I'd have on a ring you got me
using three months' worth of pay.
Uh, Sakura...
After the press conference
comes the ceremony.
Huh?!
It'd have a minimum of
five outfit changes for us.
We're both from Yamato,
so white kimonos would be perfect!
The honeymoon would be
a trip around the world, obviously.
Hey, you listening?
And then we'd move into a white house
by the ocean together.
We'd have three kids and two dogs.
On our days off, we'd all play in the water,
and there'd be a rainbow in the sky...
This is hopeless.
The brakes have come off her train of thought.
I need to do something...
Sounds good. Let's go out.
Huh?
We'll have the press conference,
do all the changing at the wedding,
go on that honeymoon, and live happily
ever after with our kids and dogs,
and a rainbow in the sky.
So how about we kiss to seal the deal?
W-Wait!
I-I actually don't have
much time to get ready.
So I'm going to stop teasing you,
and go take a bath.
She's pretty good.
Karen used to sing in the bath
when she was younger, too.
Hayato-kun.
What is it?
Could you get me my PDA?
I just thought of a good musical phrase.
I want to record it.
Sure.
Karen left her stuff all over
when she was young, too.
Hayato-kun, have you found it yet?
What are you—?
Oh, I just wanted to tidy everything up...
Never mind that!
Just give me my PDA—
Are you okay?!
Ow...
H-Here.
Th-Thanks.
Also, the bear is an exception.
It's not like I'm into that or anything.
That was bad.
Wait a second...
Women and water... Was that
what Karen was talking about?
Hayato-kun.
How do I look?
Huh?
What do you think?
I-It's cute, I guess.
That answer gets forty out of hundred.
Forty points?
What about what happened in the bathroom?
Uh, well...
I'm sorry.
Fifteen points.
What do I need to say
to get a passing grade?
Be a man and figure it out yourself.
Let's go. It's time to leave.
Y-Yeah.
What's wrong?
I think it's impressive you can handle
everyone so effortlessly like that.
Then I'm even more impressive
than you think.
Huh?
Souffle, we're done here for today, right?
Yes.
Then let's take a little detour.
What is this?
The stage for the next concert.
We expect 100,000 people to come.
100,000?!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Did you figure it out?
No, I'm not looking at your boobs.
Boobs? What are you going on about?
I knew you were dense.
Hayato-kun,
I'm trying to say that this
is my battlefield.
I'll show you.
Hundred On!
A Slayer...
This is my Hundred:
Fairy Fairytale.
She's flying.
Impressive, as always.
Oh, Professor Charlotte.
Mei-Mai's here, too.
Why are you two here?
She's going to use her Hundred
as part of her concert,
so we were called here to help.
Her type is incredibly rare.
She's a field-control type Slayer.
Field-control type...
She can create a personal field
over a specific period of time
and use her sense energy
to fly around and create illusions.
But she also can't create any weapons.
She doesn't need any weapons
to fight her fight, though.
That's right. She has her song.
Do you two know each other?
We used to be colleagues.
You could also say Charlotte
saved Sakura's life.
Her life...
I just helped her when she was
caught up in a tough situation.
It wasn't that big of a deal.
What do you think of my stage, Hayato-kun?
It's amazing. It really is!
Of course it is.
I'm the Diva of the World.
In order to repay my fans,
who have been waiting for this day,
and the staff that helped
put together this stage,
I need to put on the best concert possible.
It'll be great.
Sakura...
Yes, we're done for today.
They said I could come back
in the afternoon tomorrow.
But the plan was for you to
start in the morning tomorrow, too.
She has a song she needs to
stay in the hotel to write.
Sakura was complaining that she
wanted to go somewhere, but...
Sakura?
You're calling your client "Sakura"?
Well, Kirishima-san
told me to call her that...
If that's what the client wanted...
Come to my summer home
tomorrow morning, then.
There's something I'd like
to talk to you about.
I understand.
I can't wait—
I mean, I'll be waiting.
Huh?
Is everyone still on the island?
I guess that means
I get to be the first in the bath!
Huh?
It's locked.
Oh, it opened up.
Haya...to?
Emile, why are you...
I'm sorry.
Wait.
Want to take a bath with me?
Huh?
I used my security code to lock the door,
so I was under the impression
no one could get in, but...
We were in the same room,
so I guess our keys are the same, too.
You still haven't gotten a new one?
If I changed it out, I wouldn't be
able to get in your room anymore.
Hey...
So how was your first mission?
I think it went all right.
There was a bit of trouble partway through,
but Sakura was okay with—
Sakura?!
You're calling her "Sakura"?!
What's that about?
Call me by my name, too!
What do you mean?
I always do.
Not that!
My real name...
Emilia...
One more time.
Emilia.
Yeah.
Hayato, look.
Here, at my scar.
It's starting to fade away.
Huh?
It wasn't going away at all before.
But I guess seeing you again and
feeling better about things did the trick.
Hey, you don't have to look
so closely, you know?
You've got this pervy look on your face.
Emilia, you want to come to
the Zwei Islands tomorrow?
Are you sure?
What about your mission?
I start in the afternoon tomorrow.
Once I go finish things up with the president
in the morning, I'm free until the afternoon.
Yay! Thank you, Hayato!
Hayato, you perv!
Women and water...
Again.
Please let my song reach everyone.
And someday... that person, too...
Looks like security's pretty tight
this time, just as Vitaly said.
But Little Garden Slayers are
hardly gonna give us any trouble.
Let's go.
Well, hold your horses.
Make do with this for today.
So when are we doing it?
After the concert.
Yeah. The islanders are all excited,
so let them have their fun.
After all, we're on humanity's side.
Imitation Girl